question_data = [
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "Video streaming website YouTube was purchased in it&#039;s entirety by Facebook "
                    "for US$1.65 billion in stock.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
    },
                 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Board Games",
                  "question": "There is a Donald Trump Board Game, which was made in 1989.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
                  "question": "In the &quot;Toaru Kagaku no Railgun&quot; anime,  espers can only reach a maximum of level 6 in their abilities.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
                  "question": "In &quot;Super Mario Bros.&quot;, the clouds and bushes have the same artwork and are just different colors.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "History",
                  "question": "Kublai Khan is the grandchild of Genghis Khan?",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
                  "question": "The movie &quot;The Nightmare before Christmas&quot; was all done with physical objects.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
                  "question": "Several characters in &quot;Super Mario 64&quot; blink their eyes, including Mario himself.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Television",
                  "question": "In &quot;Star Trek&quot;, Klaang is a typical Klingon male.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science: Computers",
                  "question": "Linus Torvalds created Linux and Git.", "correct_answer": "True",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
                  "question": "Daft Punk originated in France.", "correct_answer": "True",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Art",
                  "question": "Leonardo da Vinci was not the creator of the Mona Lisa.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
                  "question": "Clefairy was intended to be Ash&#039;s starting Pok&eacute;mon in the pilot episode of the cartoon.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
                  "question": "The main playable character of the 2015 RPG &quot;Undertale&quot; is a monster.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "History",
                  "question": "The United States of America declared their independence from the British Empire on July 4th, 1776.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Geography",
                  "question": "Nova Scotia is on the east coast of Canada.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
                  "question": "The Great Wall of China is visible from the moon.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Board Games",
                  "question": "&quot;PAYDAY: The Heist&quot; is a sequel to the board game &quot;Payday&quot;.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
                  "question": "Valve&#039;s &quot;Portal&quot; and &quot;Half-Life&quot; franchises exist within the same in-game universe.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
                  "question": "In the &quot;S.T.A.L.K.E.R.&quot; series, the Freedom faction wishes to destroy the supernatural area known as  &quot;the Zone&quot;.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Animals",
                  "question": "A bear does NOT defecate during hibernation. ",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}
                 ]
